{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The Pythagorean theorem states that the square of the hypotenuse is equal to the product of the squares of the other two sides.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The proof for the Chinese Remainder Theorem used in Number Theory was NOT developed by its first publisher, Sun Tzu.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"A universal set, or a set that contains all sets, exists.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"If you could fold a piece of paper in half 50 times, its&#039; thickness will be 3\/4th the distance from the Earth to the Sun.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"E = MC3","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Zero factorial is equal to zero. ","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"A &#039;Millinillion&#039; is a real number.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In Topology, the complement of an open set is a closed set.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"You can square root a negative number with an imaginary number &quot;i&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"A scalene triangle has two sides of equal length.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}]}